well I have a periscope so you know this
if this secret click click yeah you guys
better not right Scopus you know what
no no YouTube live stop it stop it ok so
you guys remember how the Twitter said
that it was scope e100 was matching
lowest price ever a just terrible
marketing you just lie to people but B
that's even a lie so yeah no no the new
product is not a giraffe I swear it's
not a giraffe if it's a giraffe I will
give each one of you one of the new
product but it's not a charity don't get
me out the Chavez discount didn't work
I'm sorry we have a discount that does
work though I know we might have lost
your goodwill but guys October 1st is a
new product but no Whitney pilot no
that's just it no if you don't like
weekly pilot revert to the old one
that's it it's not a beanie it's not an
article of clothing guys we're not
guessing about the new product all we're
saying is you're not gonna be let down
if you buy this for 599 dollars right
now that's $100 off you can buy an eel I
know it's like hard to keep the hype up
with the new product but you won't be
sad I'm not showing you the new product
I'm showing you the new product Monday
yeah I know who let the research guy
into this dark ricardo's on vacation so
you know about giving out any more
beanies but if you don't like Wiggly
pilot I will I work on a weekly pilot
the current product has two cameras
yo mano next Monday Monday is not today
today's Wednesday I don't know what
you're thinking bro I understand you
tried to trick me I know that one if you
want to take it Yan off the shelf and
show it to the scope ease show them what
they could get for $5.99 guys come on
you got a Bible you see over there
there's actually all the eons left is
today Thursday
look at that er yeah I don't know how
I'm holding it yeah yeah daddy one could
be your yawn if you buy it is for $5.99
you can put weekly pilot on it could use
a veteran's go peace well I sign it
should we sunshine all the last of your
boxes know one of the dollars more if
you buy it right now without the coupon
I'll sign it the EON how reliable is the
Aeon yeah you buy another one that's a
great choice get one right now $5.99
Dulli on technology get more yawns
buying Aeon for your friend I know it's
a little early to start thinking about
it but eons make great Christmas gifts I
gave a neon to my dad for Christmas last
year real shit chase you can't be too
broke for Eon is $5.99 with discount
code slack e100 slack e100 buy any on
all right so my phone does not much
battery so we can't move too far I'm
using brows I'm using a Lego charger for
my phone check it out it's late charger
alright
but um you should buy more because see
that over there that's all the eons we
have left you see those for midnight
blacks they're not even for sale over
there are the last 22 eons in existence
also if you want pandas we have a lot of
those please buy pandas pandas are no
longer on Amazon by the way because fuck
Amazon
why all laugh because this is it this is
all the eons that are left you can't
trade pandas for eons the last thing I
want from anybody is pandas do you know
how much pandas we have so much pandas
you guys the October one product
replacement we're not here to talk about
the October one product we're here to
talk about the lowest price ever in
history on eons
can you come make some more well it's
not gonna be more you gotta find them
now dad I'm good wiggly pilot very
divided whether people like Wiggly pilot
go say a few words to him say a few
words Pam just provided yeah we'll give
you pandas for $92 panda you can buy
lunch I'll just go oh man look at that
box of pandas we have everything what
else can we show you have pandas Toyota
dress on the giraffes gray pandas powers
go all right here debug boys return to
yawns we have more in the bench the last
are these t-shirts
these are XL t-shirts and smalls Wow oh
there's this babe stickers get some
t-shirts all your attic guys we have me
to do it means oh yeah by some guys yeah
you don't get these stickers though
these are now this is recover three Apes
showing what we got for press that we
didn't use what we got for precision
you mean the product that we worked on
for six months and then cancer oh yeah
oh yeah we can show me we gotta the car
absolutely yeah yeah you want to pull
out a big kama yeah no we can't tell you
stocks unless you're accredited investor
yeah look at that side of that come on
you guys
it turns out cars aren't magnetic though
the court is magnetic um you can't buy
big commas but you can buy eons for $100
off with promo code slack II 100 $100
off tell us about 0.54 I don't know I
don't work on that I'm just here to
shill tonight slack e200 whoa whoa whoa
chase do you not have any on what's up
with the freon man Accord is magnetic
ever just so kill me if I told you guys
I'm going to Singapore a real shit but
um what else is real shit is eons and
you can buy them for 100 oz off look you
could have this see I would not dis dis
Yan you could really have they look like
this here and look at this Eon it's busy
on here it's not gonna be yours because
it's ours but they all look just like
this one we promise cuz we bought it
from the shop we go to the shop to you
know what else we bought from the shop a
panda paw rare the rare red paw you know
whatever purple all purple paws are
there gpause those are real crazy like I
said check it out gray pandas these ones
work yeah
someone by your pandas yeah so we buy my
damage we have like way too many are you
gonna have to take out a second mortgage
to afford the new product no no don't
worry they're gonna be let down by the
new product it's a giraffe giraffe
no I'm kidding I swear it's not a
giraffe giraffe it comes in a box
do we have an empty box that we could
show them to get them hyped for just the
size of the product what just the comma
side of the box is one of my desk over
there what oh yeah yeah guys you want to
see the box oh yeah look at that box
that's the box the new product comes in
but you should buy a neon talking we're
just talking what other guys in research
was like you know I've never even used a
giraffe but it sounds like a shitty
product stop trying to sell things in my
channel okay
slack II one hundred the Box justifies
the price you don't even know what the
price is that's not to be announced yet
is it another animal name it's not an
animal name it's not clothes and it's
not a giraffe just what you know and you
know the box there's no more hints for
the product you have to wait till Monday
we're getting more box you want to see
more box no um what we might do them
we're gonna scope you Monday viv is
coming for that we're gonna present it
at a real presentation with journalists
and this coming and she'll scope Ian
today's not Monday stop trying to trick
me no but you guys let me tell you about
the new product we have 22 Young's left
and if we don't sell them there's no new
product we're delaying it
I don't know if they do product in the
unreplaceable no no um put it this way
you won't be upset if you buy a neon
unless you're very caught but I
shouldn't say anything else guys you
can't me to give away so much secrets
you know I love giving away secrets the
new product goes on sale once we sell
the 22 EOS or Monday and by that I mean
just Monday but if we don't sell the 22
eons we're cancelling it and you'll
never see the new product um you're
assuming you'll get a new product if you
buy a neon will new product be sold on
Monday I can't talk about any of that it
could be a pre-order it could just be
hype it could just be the box it could
just be a box for your er pretty good
product right
it's yond you fold it yourself it comes
in a big envelope it's an eon carrying
case box yes okay maybe it's the big
comma maybe we actually know you can't
buy the box now because on the other
side of the box it says what the product
is so you can't do that Eon XS max even
10's max um yo I got a red case for my
iPhone last night I went to the Apple
store and I was gonna buy an iPhone this
is true story Jeff at the Apple store no
I went to the Apple store and I was like
waffling we got there at like 7:40 and I
was like should I buy the frame I was
wobbling what should I buy it shouldn't
not okay sorry Skokie's um should I buy
it should I not buy it should I buy it
should not buy and eventually alex is
like heard you're never gonna be happy
if you don't buy it and I was like oh
it's will I ever be happy no matter what
I do and she's like that's a good
question but we agreed to buy the iPhone
the time was now 801 and they're like
it's after 8:00 we can't do live phone
sales after 8:00 what's under their
clothes hey so
so yeah I didn't buy the iPhone but you
could feel my cases so I just plug a
case for my iPhone X and like I think I
just pretend that you're not blocked I
can read you they close at 8:00 you have
the Apple on Chestnut Street and then we
went to the beach
you're not blocked it's like buying beer
in Utah yeah I know real shit
pedalboards it Awards no we don't we
don't send pedal boards out oh you
shorten pedal boards no chase chase ones
cuddle for a civic guys you know what
this is it's the inside of a but ya know
guys you got to buy Aeons come on
they're $100 off tell your friends it's
a perfect time to get started and buy
yawns chicanery system decision who'd
you sell it to
did you tell them it was broke can we do
some research into a honda eps hack now
do machine learning you guys are
dangerous that's right do it do it
Oh if you come work here you get EPS
hack to tell your friends tell your
friends to apply for a job for hire
you can verify you repair panda all
perfect I'll chase you or you work for
us your printer Jase you're working hard
back there right now you want to go look
at the printers I think we might have
enough battery car we are hiring check
out our hiring page thank you for the
super heart can you be tools and you do
know things about tools in firmware
firmware engineer leave firmware
engineer
I'm totally autos without hybrid you
stop and go you have to ask walks or for
his Toyota pence yeah we have the great
coffee together Eddie yeah Eddie makes
great coffee cold brew cold brew which
car is the most torque
to work with a lag get you on - by Neal
and I keep slide what black thing Oh
block the phone some slack
maybe I'm gonna slide later I sure got
the iPhone access I think this yeah
alright guys but this is a slide pretty
easy on these these are rare one of the
cranky on you'll be able to sell just a
box on ebay someday when we're rich and
famous get some get some these could be
yours
some people have signed boxes get me so
all I did side things are the two of us
are we doing the two it this year maybe
you know guys you really you gotta buy
yarns they don't buy any Elms yet no
refresh
no no body yawns come on guys
there are a hundred dollars off you're
never gonna get a better deal than this
on me on because on Monday the new
product comes out
don't buy a shirt yeah buy a shirt what
we'll shout out yeah placed an order
tell her I put buy things okay I'll sign
one of the scope e this e one will be
signed yeah we have a nice marker for me
well I have a Sharpie in there cubby
we're getting a sharpie I'm gonna sign
the back of this box whoever buys the
next Aeon gets this signed yawn I'm not
signing your damn shirt they're only 20
dollars all right I'm gonna sign it real
nice geo ha
guys if you buy this neon I signed it
what sign inside of you
I'm gonna yeah one sign in this eon
whole common team
check out this eon whoever buys the next
eon gets this one signed Georgie boy and
I'll buy it if you assume you won't buy
it and then I'll sign it
I want to face it with that shit what
model is it this is a 64 gigabyte base
model Eon it's the only Eon we still
have for sale everything else is sold
out so you can buy this Eon right here
you'll buy too if I give you an
interview yeah yeah bye - and I'll give
you an interview right now yeah go bye -
right now we're gonna do it I'll give
you an innovate but don't have to do it
in person if we do it on the phone right
after the scoping in phone right after
this Gopi let's do it I'm seriously down
I'll talk to you about whatever shit you
watched by - yawns oh he says he bought
a shirt who bought a shirt no you can't
buy midnight blacks they're sold out
yeah look did you buy a shirt yeah he
bought a shirt
oh let's uselessness only $20 that
literally cost us more to fulfillment
this is a midnight Blacky on but you
can't buy because they're a stop just
for us you're just for us thanks Tyler
thank you for buying a shirt no we
really do appreciate it every little bit
helps
you know guys we're trying to be a
profitable company otherwise Karma's
gonna go away because we're never
raising money from scumbag venture
capitalists again hope the venture
capitalists are watching they know this
complex but you get this nice signed
yawn oh you want a job interview oh yeah
email give me a job at come AI goodbye -
yawns - pr's and asked me if like how do
you feel about the security
of we don't know like I'm okay with
trading media attention for hype we're
for money the job interviews we can't
take that process
that's like bribing a judge can't bribe
judges for that but we can certainly
bribe judges for media interviews that's
fine because the media is corrupt that's
right
and will be corrupt just like the media
if it means we're rich they won't buy
anything yet
well we can let's watch it live on the
analytics oh yeah click analytics for
visitors right now who's checking out oh
we got four people checking out yeah
yeah by that beyonds you'll buy there me
owns two purchased oh I love watching
these numbers go up Chase bought a shirt
so chased by a shirt look there's an oh
there's an order
yeah whoo two shirts but on the shirts
you wanna buy a grape and a antenna
mount anybody check out these grape an
antenna mounts you can buy one it comes
with a grape and a 5-second can't buy
them separate no no sweatshirts are
never coming interview you know what we
have a lot of now comma power yeah yeah
we had a well guys want comma powers if
you're having errors with your Toyota
make sure you buy a comm tower or a boss
Honda we don't run a giraffe's soon yeah
no we're almost out guys better find
your house now why no PayPal Bugsy this
Bugsy find in New York oh yeah by that
young
no we don't have played throw sorry we
might have not a flame thrower
not a planter that's possible that's how
I bought one you bought enough like dark
then I canceled oh are you sure bring
it'll work
wait usually the scope he tells me how
long I've been scoping for I'm something
this doesn't tell me guys how wait we
can just check Twitter how long Elevens
go being for this is not going more than
30 minutes I'm a South Park to watch 21
minutes guys this is an ultra rare white
yeah
one plus three you can't buy this one
but you can buy an eon probably Bugsy
yeah leo boards this was that eyo boards
the South Park on tourists a hole there
anymore boards from Neos we have a lot
of doctors oh oh man I don't even know
about your closest person's name out cuz
they might not want their name said
publicly but we just solved an ER woo yo
that's Lackey 100 you're getting the
sign Deion I'll sign another on if
anyone will buy him there are no
shortages of pause if anyone would like
pause here's 200 pause to set to pause
[Laughter]
$99 comedy bugs you can buy that with
the money you save on Annie young
debug ridiculous product they haven't
seen how many shirts you need to buy for
you to send me the new product instead
well we have a lot Bansi before yeah
that's worth now that might come back
[Music]
here's a moto G smartphone yeah the
latest it's just a normal Moto G
smartphone there's nothing special about
it
it's always signing another one yet mark
will sign them right now it's good man
yeah bye guys bye
yawns was the with a sharpie oh yeah
watch this one you're gonna sign a.m.
drop no it's not a giraffe I told her
it's time to wrap no not yeah band the
bots oh the size of that signature you
want their service box change oh well I
know about that did anyone reply to that
by the way no cameras okay you can get
the large signature key on get that
large signature Y on right now buy that
shit we'll keep them like this is the PI
almost shipping like that order yeah
remember just purchase large thickness
garlic we just saw neon I think so
oh my god we saw two eons wani are now
what was $40 wait wait the orders are
pouring in oh man oh we're selling he
owns like crazy
yeah yo I'm so happy with all of you
thank you for buying me on
all right I will sign one more I will
sign one more except instead of signing
it we're actually just gonna put a dot
on this one dot no no no I will sign it
if you'll buy it but it only is a small
signature the big segments just sold out
it does come with a dot though
what are we gonna ship uh tomorrow yeah
we'll ship if you buy eons we will all
the ear insults and I can find anyone
who buys a neon wall this periscopes
going on will sign it will give you $100
off and we will ship it out to you
tomorrow
[Laughter]
well start we'll start all the unboxes
to go out tonight yeah if you missed a
sign to yard yeah you know that's just
the way the cookie crumbles
[Music]
guys we're at $1,700 in sales today keep
buying eons
when's the Aeon end-of-life date don't
worry about that how about this I will
tell you this the next product is
completely compatible with the Aeon so
we'll run all the same software as the
Aeon so no big deal there don't worry
about like any other end of life there
will be any on end of life but it's not
this problem so don't worry about that
if that's if that's holding you back
from buying a neon in fact the Aeons
will work a little bit better for a bit
cuz we got to try new models am I still
living in the home office can you buy an
e on board no run it better or worse
it's compatible it's very compatible
indoors to live here yeah I love
upstairs guys we've got a cup by eons
but how much time is dependant 30 miles
is Kobey's 27 27 right we got three more
minutes come on oh no the reading fixed
families are there does anyone like
watch these and see all the secrets that
are revealed for young cool right no no
no no no but but get in right now buy a
neon buy stop with so much stuff what a
great panel we have gray panda deadness
great panda this one could be yours
well sign gray pandas we will sign the
Aeons how hard is to get the CEO
position so easy I've never been happier
bros but I still do the scope he's some
of them all right guys could we get one
more ye on sale before the periscope is
out was having Elsa no oh he gets big
signature oh he get big thing is your
guy and you got gets double signature
you're welcome thank you thank you
people we love it when you buy eelain's
you won't regret your decision you might
regret your decision I don't know if
you'll get your decision yeah I'm not
taking paypal absolutely not
after what they did to move out Jones
that's never PayPal again I hated PayPal
for a long time people took PayPal stole
$10,000 from me once so we're never
using PayPal mafia
yeah PayPal mafia yeah I'm not using
Ilan wool shit I'm okay though actually
the worst if you've ever tried to work
with them Amazon is terrible as well we
use Shopify for payments shop finds
great love Shopify oh yeah no I I got
like a hundred K in donations in Pape I
was like working a freeze 10k event like
can you unfreeze it and they're like no
so it was frozen for like two years
until I kept complaining and then they
unfrozen
please ship your panda please I need it
urgently yes
huh my Twitter stock doing I don't know
we could check my Robin Hood yeah I did
show that hey wait that's a twitchy
thing alright it looks like who we gods
is what we're selling right now guys
that you know the the discount it's not
gonna last forever the discounts gonna
go away on Monday I got donations no no
no that was donations for a black rain
there's donations for black rain when
PayPal took ten of my thousand dollars
um they did let me have my lawyer
donations they're not that much of dicks
can't watch my twitch do you should
subscribe to my twitch I love making
money on twitch um but I also love
making money on Skokie's so make sure to
buy it you all right thank you all for
watching that's all bye Skokie's new
product announcement on Monday it's
gonna be crazy
you just like the fire festival you know
it's gonna be it's gonna be crazy
big big leak that's so weird all right
back